Remember
whispers in the dark Just a flicker, not a spark A
house of shadows, paper thin Never knew where to
begin You came along, a guiding light And turned
the darkness into bright You found the key, you
built the door A thing we never had before
And in this house on Lisa Court You built our one
and only port A steady roof, a solid floor You
gave us that and so much more Yeah, in this house
on Lisa Court You are our rock, our last resort
You gave us a place to finally land With your
loving, steady hand.
The simple sound of your car key is the sound of
safety wild and free. The smell of dinner on the
stove, a testament to your true love. No need to
hide, no need to brace in this quiet, gentle,
sacred space. You drew a line against the past, a
sanctuary built to last.
And in this house on Lisa Court You built our one
and only port A steady roof, a solid floor You
gave us that and so much more Yeah, in this house
on Lisa Court You are our rock, our last resort
You gave us a place to finally land With your
loving, steady hand
And in this house on Lisa Court You built our one
and only port A steady roof, a solid floor You
gave us that and so much more Yeah, in this house
on Lisa Court You are our rock, our last resort
You gave us a place to finally land With your love
Steady hand